JACOB MOORE

Student

jacob.moore0081@gmail.com +64 22 139 3760 https://www.linkedin.com/in/jacobmoore-6083191a8/

I am a 22 year old student living in Hamilton and have just completed my study at Waikato University. My work experience includes attributes relating to customer service, being able to do tasks efficiently, and being able to stay focused in a stressful environment. My peers and coworkers have described me as dedicated, responsible, and highly motivated. I can remain enthusiastic when working in high pressure environments and consider myself a good worker who takes pride in my work. I enjoy working with people, I am friendly and polite, but I can also deal with difficult customers when needed. I enjoy learning new skills as well as developing my existing skills and I can effectively establish relationships with customers.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SALES CONSULTANT

Noel Leeming February 2022 - Present Te Rapa

As a part of the sales team, my responsibilities include:

- Ensuring customer satisfaction before, during, and continuing after the purchase is made.
- Completing sales goals and achieving KPIs.
- Maintaining a high level of professionalism.
- Sharing knowledge and advice with customers and co-workers about various products we sell.
- Studying and developing expertise in new products and models when they release.

INTERN

AFFCO New Zealand July 2022 - November 2022 Horotiu

As an intern for the Hakarimata team at AFFCO, my responsibilities included:

- · Assisting in system migration
- Data preparation and analysis
- Developing training management tools
- Streamlining logistics and distribution systems

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Bachelor of Management Studies
University of Waikato
2019 - 2022
Economics, Strategic Management
Honours

Hamilton Boys' High School 2014 - 2018

CORE SKILLS

- Highly reliable and responsible
- Ability to excel under pressure
- Good sense of initiative
- Technical ability
- People skills
- Organisational knowledge
- Clear communication
- Ability to work in a team or individually
- Good interpersonal skills

KEY STRENGTHS

- Critical Analyst
- Respectful Collaborator
- Hunger to Learn